A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1 FA429
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
1966-1999
1979-1989
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund.
FA429
27.73 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Other Finding Aids note
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Rockefeller Archive Center acquired a major portion of the Commonwealth Fund archives in 1986. This initial deposit included fifty-five cubic feet of administrative records and fellowship files from the Fund's Harkness Fellowship offices in New York and London. Subsequent transfers of records have continued as necessary.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Arrangement
The Margaret E. Mahoney papers are arranged in 5 subseries: Subseries 1. Board of Directors. Subseries 2. General Files. Subseries 3. Personal Correspondence. Subseries 4. Speeches. Subseries 5. Accession 1995.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: meeting minutes, correspondence, speeches, and reports.
Hygiene; Education, Rural; Child welfare; Law; War relief; Child psychology; Medicine, Rural; Child mental health; Legal issues; Medical education; Public welfare; Public health; Legal research; Mental health; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; New York (State); United States; New York (N.Y.); Medical research
- Board of Directors, 1
  - General Expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1980 July 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1980 May-Sept.3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1981 Feb., May-June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1981 July, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1982 Sept.-Oct. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1983 April-May (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1983 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Investment Policy, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Investment Policy, 1981 May-June (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Investment Policy, 1981 June-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 238th Board Meeting, 1980 Feb.-May 8 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Special Board Meeting - Report on New Program Directions, 1980 Sept. 25 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 239th Board Meeting, 1980 Nov. 13 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 62nd Annual Meeting of the Corporation, 1980 Nov. 13 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 240th Board Meeting, 1981 Feb. 8 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 241st Board Meeting, 1981 May 13 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 242nd Board Meeting, 1981 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 63rd Annual Meeting of the Corporation, 1981 Nov. 23 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 243rd Board Meeting, 1981 Nov. 23 (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
  - Nominations Committee Meeting, 1980-1982 April 13 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Plimpton, Calvin H., 1984 June 11 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Temps, Consultants, Book Budget, and Local Expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Travel Expenses and Budget Sheets, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Under Consideration, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- General Files, 2
  Arrangement
  Folder contents arranged both alphabetically and further arranged in reverse chronology.
  - Correspondence, 1
    - Acknowledgment Letters - to be done, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Articles - Business & Health, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Beaver College, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Beaver College, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Brochures - Academic Medicine for Minority Students, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Brochures - Commonwealth Fund, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Brochures - Grants Management Reprints, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - New Program Brochure - Reprints, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Program Brochure Reprints, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Budget Expenses and Travel, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 38-40)
    - Budget Sheets & Travel, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Carnegie Corporation - Health Program, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Carnegie Corporation - Reprints, 1935,1951, 1955, 1959, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Carnegie Corporation - Reprints, 1963, 1970, 1980, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Carnegie Corporation - Samaritan Health Service, 1970-1972, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Christmas Card List, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Christmas Party, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Christmas Party, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Chronicles on Higher Education - Harkness Fellows, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Clippings - AIDS, 1987 july-Aug. (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Clippings - Alcohol/Abuse, 1987 July (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Clippings - Commonwealth Fund, 1987 June-July (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Clippings - Drugs, 1987 May (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Clippings - Employment, 1987 May (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Clippings - Financial, 1987 May (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Clippings - Foundations, 1987 June-July (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Clippings - General, 1987 Aug. (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Clippings - Grants, 1987 May-June (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Clippings - Minority Education, 1987 June (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Clippings - NYC Commission on the Year 2000, 1987 May-Aug. (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Clippings - Poverty, 1987 July (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Clippings - Women, 1987 May (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Clipping Files, 1987 July-Aug. (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Clipping Files, 1987 Aug. (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Committee on Peace and International Cooperation - Letters of Interest, 1989 Oct. (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Commonwealth Histories, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Conference/Information, 1979, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Conference Sites, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Congress Bill - s.1857, 1983 Oct.-Nov., 1984 Feb. 28 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Congressional Hearings, 1983 May-Nov. (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Congressional Hearings - COF Press Conference, 1983 June 22-23 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Congressional Hearings - Letters to John J. Salmon - MEM's Second Testimony to Congress, 1983 July (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Congressional Hearings - MEM',s U.S. H.O.R. Testimony Final, 1983 June 22 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Congressional Hearings - Meeting at Harkness House - Hearing on Foundations, 1983 Jan. 31 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Congressional Hearings - Related Correspondence, 1983 Jan.-Aug. (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Congressional Liason, 1983 Feb. (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Dinners, 1986, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Distinguishing Among Teaching Hospitals, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Elderly, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Elderly - Clippings, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Elderly - General, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Elderly - Health, Housing and Health Care, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Elderly - Medicare Health Insurance, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Elderly - Perceptions, Stereotypes and Longevity, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Elderly - Press Clippings, 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Elderly - Social Security, Pensions & Retirement, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Flinn Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Ford Foundation, 1979-1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Foundations - Pediatrics Support, 1973-1980 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Frankel Tributes, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Grant Foundations, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Hangslips, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Hartford Foundation, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Harkness Fellowship - Selection Committee Meeting, London, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Hilton Head, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Histories/Budget, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Hunter College Course - Did Not Go, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Invoice Production - Association Litho & Letter Service, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Invoice Production - Curtis & Company, 1985, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Invoice Production - Free Lance Bills, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Invoice Production - Invoices, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Invoice Production - Mailing House, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Invoice Production - PIPR, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Itineraries, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 104-106)
    - Itinerary Proposed, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Letters of Congratulations, 1980 April-May (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Letters of Congratulations, 1980 April- May (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Letters of Congratulations, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Letters Logged in by EM, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Letters Reappointments - Answered Letters, 1980 May-June (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Letters of Reappointment - Letters of Congratulations, 1980 April-May 1980 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Mac Arthur Foundation, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Mac Arthur Foundation, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Mc Dermott, Walsh, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Media Interviews, Clippings and Publications, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Meetings - Administrative Meetings - JC/TWM/JRM - 530 East 72nd Street, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Meetings - Atherton Meetings, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Meetings - Robert Ebert, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Meetings - Sims Farr - Lunches, 1980's (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Meetings - Future Planning, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Meetings - Gail Potter, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Meetings - JEC/TWM Meetings, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Meetings - JC/MEM, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - Meetings - Moskin, R./Potter, G., 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Meetings - Nielsen, Waldemar, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - Meetings - J. Robert Moskin, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Meetings - Nora Piore, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Meetings - Staff Lunch Talks, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Meetings - Staff Meetings - Every Other Tuesday with Exceptions, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - Meetings - TWM/MEM Weekly Meetings, 1983 July 7 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - Meetings - U.S. Cities, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - Milbank Foundation, 1971, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Muskiwinni Foundation, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - NYC Hearings on Tax Exemptions - MEM's Testimony, 1983 June 16, Dec. (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - NYC Hearings on Tax Exceptions - Related Correspondence, 1983 May-June (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - NY Society of Fellows, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Press Clippings - Service & Information, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - Press Releases - Fund, 1981-1986 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Prime of Your Life TV Program, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Problems Facing Elderly Americans Living Alone - Fund Related Publications, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Problems Facing Elderly Americans Living Alone - Old, Alone & Poor, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Problems Facing Elderly Americans Living Alone - Study, 1986 June-July (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Problems Facing Elderly Americans Living Alone - First Draft and Elderly People Living Alone, 1987 Jan.-Feb. (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Proposal List Agendas, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Program Opportunities Brochure - Invoices, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Program Press Releases, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - Publications Status Reports, 1986 Nov. 7 (Box 15, Folder 149)
    - Recommendation Letters, 1979-1983 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - Recommendation Letters, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - Recommendation Letters - Delbanco - IOM Nomination, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 152)
    - Recommendation Letters - TWM/AAAS, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - Recommendation Letters - TWM/OTA, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 154)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1980-1986 (Box 15, Folder 155)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation - Grants in Trouble, 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 156)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation - Program Planning & Procedure, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 157)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 158)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1978-1979, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 159)
    - S, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - Task Force - Academic Health Center - Activities, Grants & Meetings, 1983-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - Task Force - Fellowship Program in Academic Medicine for Minority Students, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - Task Force - Miscellaneous Information, 1986 July-Oct. (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - Teaching Programs Budget, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 165)
    - W.M. Keck Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - Pink Chronological Correspondence
      - 1980 Dec. (Box 17, Folder 167)
      - 1981 Jan.-Feb. (Box 17, Folder 168)
      - 1981 March-April (Box 17, Folder 169)
      - 1981 May-June (Box 17, Folder 170)
      - 1981 June-July (Box 18, Folder 171)
      - 1981 Aug.-Sept. (Box 18, Folder 172)
      - 1981 Oct.-Nov. (Box 18, Folder 173)
      - 1981 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 174)
      - 1982 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 175)
      - 1982 Feb.-March (Box 18, Folder 176)
      - 1982 April-May (Box 19, Folder 177)
      - 1982 July-Aug. (Box 19, Folder 178)
      - 1982 Sept.-Oct. (Box 19, Folder 179)
      - 1982 Nov. (Box 19, Folder 180)
      - 1982 Dec. (Box 19, Folder 181)
      - Blainey and Hinde Dinner, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 182)
      - 1983 Jan.-Feb. (Box 20, Folder 183)
      - 1983 March (Box 20, Folder 184)
      - 1983 April-May (Box 20, Folder 185)
      - 1983 June-July (Box 20, Folder 186)
      - 1983 Aug.-Sept. (Box 20, Folder 187)
      - 1983 Oct.-Nov. (Box 21, Folder 188)
      - 1983 Nov.-Dec. (Box 21, Folder 189)
      - 1984 Jan.-Feb. (Box 21, Folder 190)
      - 1984 Feb.-March (Box 21, Folder 191)
      - 1984 April-May (Box 21, Folder 192)
      - 1984 June-July (Box 22, Folder 193)
      - 1984 Aug.-Sept. (Box 22, Folder 194)
      - 1984 Oct.-Nov. (Box 22, Folder 195)
      - 1984 Dec. (Box 22, Folder 196)
      - 1985 Jan.-Feb. (Box 22, Folder 197)
      - 1985 March-April (Box 22, Folder 198)
      - 1985 May-June (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1985 July-Sept. (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1985 Sept.-Oct. (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1985 Nov.-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 202)
      - 1986 Jan.-Feb. (Box 23, Folder 203)
      - 1986 March-April (Box 23, Folder 204)
      - 1986 May-June (Box 24, Folder 205)
      - 1986 July-Aug. (Box 24, Folder 206)
      - So - Sociology, 1986 Sept.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 207)
      - Timothy E. Wirth, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - Unemployment, 1987 Jan.-June (Box 25, Folder 209)
      - 1989 Jan.-Feb. (Box 25, Folder 210)
      - 1989 Feb.-March (Box 25, Folder 211)
      - 1989 April-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 212)
      - 1989 Oct.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 213)
  - Indexes, 2
    - A, 1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 214)
    - B, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 215)
    - B, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 215A)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Closed from Scholarly Access
    - C, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 216)
    - D, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 217)
    - E, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 218)
    - E, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 218A)
      No Subnote Content
    - F, 1981-1084 (Box 26, Folder 219)
    - F, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 219A)
    - G, 1979, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 220)
    - H-I, 1979-1984 (Box 26, Folder 221)
    - H-I, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 221A)
    - J, 1979-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 222)
    - K, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 223)
    - L, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 224)
    - M, 1979-1984 (Box 27, Folder 225)
    - N, 1979, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - O, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 227)
    - P-Q, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 228)
    - R, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 229)
    - R, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 229A)
    - S, 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 230)
    - T-V, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 231)
    - W, 1981, 1984,1986 (Box 27, Folder 232)
    - W, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 232A)
    - X-Z, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 233)
    - A-D, 1980-1988 (Box 27, Folder 234)
    - E-H, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 235)
    - J-M, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 236)
    - P, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 237)
    - Q-W, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 238)
    - General Files - Correspondences - Indexes A-D, 1980-1988; 2015:FA429:001 (Item 2015:FA429:001)
    - A-B, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 239)
    - B-C, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 240)
    - C-F, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 241)
    - G-H, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 242)
    - H-J, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 243)
    - J-L, 1987-1989 (Box 29, Folder 244)
    - M, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 245)
    - N-O, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 246)
    - P-R, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 247)
    - R-S, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 248)
    - S-W, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 249)
    - W-Y, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 250)
    - A, 1988-1994 (Box 31, Folder 251)
    - B, 1988-1994 (Box 31, Folder 252)
    - C, 1988-1994 (Box 31, Folder 253)
    - D, 1988-1994 (Box 31, Folder 254)
    - E, 1981, 1988-1993 (Box 32, Folder 255)
    - F, 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 256)
    - General Files - Correspondence - Indexes F, 1989; 2015:FA429:003 (Item 2015FA429:003)
    - F, 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 257)
    - G, 1988-1994 (Box 32, Folder 258)
    - H, 1986-1994 (Box 32, Folder 259)
    - I, 1989, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 260)
    - J, 1988-1994 (Box 32, Folder 261)
    - K, 1982-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 33, Folder 262)
    - L, 1988-1994 (Box 33, Folder 263)
    - M, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 264)
    - M, 1990-1994 (Box 33, Folder 265)
    - N, 1988-1994 (Box 34, Folder 266)
    - O, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 267)
    - P-Q, 1988-1994 (Box 34, Folder 268)
    - R, 1982, 1986, 1989-1994 (Box 34, Folder 269)
    - S, 1987-1991 (Box 34, Folder 270)
    - S, 1991-1994 (Box 35, Folder 271)
    - T, 1988-1994 (Box 35, Folder 272)
    - U, 1988, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 273)
    - V, 1987, 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 274)
    - W, 1988-1992 (Box 35, Folder 275)
    - W, 1989-1994 (Box 35, Folder 276)
    - X-Y-Z, 1988-1993 (Box 35, Folder 277)
    - General Files - Correspondence - Indexes - F, 1988-1992; 2015 :FA429:002 (Item 2015:FA429:002)
  - Mail Logs, 3
    - Mail Logs, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 278)
    - Mail Logs, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 279)
    - Mail Logs, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 280)
    - Mail Logs, 1982 Jan.-June (Box 36, Folder 281)
    - Mail Logs, 1982 July-Dec. (Box 36, Folder 282)
    - Mail Logs, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 283)
    - Mail Logs, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 284)
    - Mail Logs, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 285)
    - Mail Logs, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 286)
    - Mail Logs, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 287)
    - Mail Logs, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 288)
  - Phone Logs, 4
    - Phone Logs, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 289)
    - Phone Logs, 1983 March-Aug. (Box 38, Folder 290)
    - Phone Logs, 1983 Aug.-Dec. (Box 38, Folder 291)
    - Phone Logs, 1984 Jan.-June (Box 38, Folder 292)
    - Phone Logs, 1984 June-Nov. (Box 38, Folder 293)
    - Phone Logs, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 294)
    - Phone Logs, 1985 April-May (Box 39, Folder 295)
    - Phone Logs, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 296)
    - Phone Logs, 1986 Jan.-July (Box 39, Folder 297)
    - Phone Logs, 1986 Aug.-Dec. (Box 39, Folder 298)
    - Phone Logs, 1987 Jan.-May (Box 39, Folder 299)
    - Phone Logs, 1987 June-Dec. (Box 40, Folder 300)
    - Phone Logs, 1988 Jan.-June (Box 40, Folder 301)
    - Phone Logs, 1988 July-Dec. (Box 40, Folder 302)
    - Phone Logs, 1989 Jan.-June (Box 40, Folder 303)
    - Phone Logs, 1989 July-Dec. (Box 40, Folder 304)
- Personal Correspondence, 3
  Folder contents arranged both alphaetically and further arranged in reverse chronology.
  - Appointment Books, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 305)
  - Appointment Books, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 306)
  - Appointment Books, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 307)
  - Appointment Books, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 308)
  - Artist Friends, 1966-1970, 1986, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 309)